<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cloud Chemistry</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Premium eLiquid Custom Handmade to Order™</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 02:40:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.3</generator>
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">132433436</site>	<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Believe the Hype</title>
		<link>/dont-believe-the-hype/</link>
					<comments>/dont-believe-the-hype/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 02:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=23455</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LcCeaBYYeBM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/dont-believe-the-hype/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">23455</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stop the Flavor Ban</title>
		<link>/stop-the-flavor-ban/</link>
					<comments>/stop-the-flavor-ban/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=23187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As you most likely have heard by now on the main stream hype media, vaping is facing an existential threat, and we all need to pull together in solidarity in &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="ast-button" href="/stop-the-flavor-ban/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Stop the Flavor Ban</span> Read More »</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As you most likely have heard by now on the main stream hype media, vaping is facing an existential threat, and we all need to pull together in solidarity in order to safeguard our future, and to protect our right to use safer alternatives to smoking.</p>



<p>In addition to individual states like Michigan announcing flavored eLiquid bans, now President Trump has announced that he will seek a federal ban on flavored eLiquid products. This news comes in the aftermath of a recent bout of serious lung-related illnesses that the news outlets are saying were caused by &#8220;vaping&#8221;. But is this true?</p>



<p>While health officials continue to investigate the precise causes of these illnesses, we do know one thing to be true:</p>



<p>These illnesses were most likely caused by vaporizing and inhaling oil, not eLiquid. Specifically, cannabis THC/CBD vaporizers, blackmarket cartridges, and vape-able vitamins, such as Vitamin E, are all the primary suspects. However, this distinction is not being made in headlines, causing confusion in the eyes of the general public. When people see “vape,” they think eLiquid. As members of the vape community, we all know oil and juice are not even close to being the same thing.</p>



<p>Enhancing eLiquid with flavors not only provides a more pleasant vaping experience, it facilitates an easier transition into vaping and away from the harmfully addictive vice grip of tobacco products. Thousands of people depend on flavored eLiquid as a safer alternative to toxic, combustible cigarettes.</p>



<p>Please take a moment to sign the official <em>We The People Petition</em> to get our voices in front of policy makers who have the power to shield us from impending doom!</p>



<p><a href="https://petitions.whitehouse.gov/petition/stop-donald-trump-signing-federal-flavor-ban-e-cig-products">https://petitions.whitehouse.gov/petition/stop-donald-trump-signing-federal-flavor-ban-e-cig-products</a></p>



<p>Also, tweet your positive eLiquid story and tag President Trump:</p>



<p><a href="https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1172639954985455616">https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1172639954985455616</a></p>



<p>Be sure to share the above links with your friends!</p>



<p>At CloudChemistry, we have always valued the safety of our customers—and of ourselves! We all vape our eLiquid exclusively. That’s why we only source regulated, verified and tested materials for our flavor concentrate inventory. Quality and safety is of the utmost importance to us, and we strongly urge the vaping community at large to use only verified, tested materials in their eLiquid.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/stop-the-flavor-ban/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">23187</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Know Nicotine</title>
		<link>/know-nicotine/</link>
					<comments>/know-nicotine/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Nicotine Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=21405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The team behind the groundbreaking and influential documentary A Billion Lives is hard at work producing a sequel that they&#8217;re tagging with the catchy title Know Nicotine. Aaron Biebert, of &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="ast-button" href="/know-nicotine/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Know Nicotine</span> Read More »</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The team behind the groundbreaking and influential documentary <a href="https://abillionlives.com/">A Billion Lives</a> is hard at work producing a sequel that they&#8217;re tagging with the catchy title <a href="https://knownicotine.com/">Know Nicotine</a>.</p>



<p>Aaron Biebert, of <em>A Billion Lives</em> fame, is also heading up this new project as its director. He is traveling around pitching the film as <a href="https://www.facebook.com/tmj4/videos/vb.79146833756/2241062876111080/">cutting edge research in the area of nicotine</a>. He says the film aims to vindicate the unjustly stigmatized chemical by shedding light on its many, and largely unknown, positive attributes. According to Biebert, the film will present scientific research which solidly demonstrates the health improvements many adults could see by using nicotine.</p>



<p>We&#8217;re kicking off our new <em>Nicotine</em> blog post series by plugging this documentary. Stay tuned for more nicotine related posts to follow.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/know-nicotine/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">21405</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>We&#8217;re Moving!</title>
		<link>/we-are-moving/</link>
					<comments>/we-are-moving/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=20011</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dear loyal patrons, With the changing of the seasons, change comes also to Cloud Chemistry. It is with great pride and excitement that we make the following announcements: Flagship Store &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="ast-button" href="/we-are-moving/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">We&#8217;re Moving!</span> Read More »</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Dear loyal patrons,</h2>
<p>With the changing of the seasons, change comes also to Cloud Chemistry.</p>
<p>It is with great pride and excitement that we make the following announcements:</p>
<h4>Flagship Store in East Stroudsburg is Moving</h4>
<p>On Tuesday, October 16, our flagship store located in Eagle Valley at 748 Milford Rd, East Stroudsburg, will relocate to the Price Chopper Shopping Plaza, 4543 Milford Rd, East Stroudsburg.</p>
<p>The Eagle Valley location will remain open for one additional week, and close on Monday, October 22, in order to allow our customers ample time to adapt to the change.</p>
<h4>New Location in Montage Mountain (Scranton)</h4>
<p>We continue to expand our dominant presence throughout Northeast, PA, with the opening of our third retail location in Montage Mountain, outside of Scranton.</p>
<p>Our regular <a href="/locations/">Locations</a> page will be kept updated with the latest information.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/we-are-moving/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">20011</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gift Cards Are Now Available for Purchase</title>
		<link>/introducing-gift-cards/</link>
					<comments>/introducing-gift-cards/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 16:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=18210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Happy is the heart that gives, especially when it gives custom eLiquid. 😀]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="blog-post-intro">In response to popular demand, we are happy to now offer gift cards.</p>
<p>The next time you&#8217;re in the giving mood, we&#8217;ve made the gift-card buying process extremely simple.</p>
<p>Some things to note:</p>
<ul>
<li>Gift cards are issued in the form of store credit <em>redemption codes</em> which are redeemable <strong>only</strong> in our online store.</li>
<li>Gift cards can be purchased in any denomination or quantity.</li>
</ul>
<p>That&#8217;s all there is to it. Now go spread the love.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;margin:2rem 0;"><a href="/gift-cards" class="button">Give some eLiquid!</a></div>
<p><strong>Quick Note:</strong></p>
<p>Don&#8217;t forget, if you&#8217;re the sort of happy customer to buy our stuff as a gift for a loved one, then you&#8217;re also likely to be the type who&#8217;d benefit from our <a href="/introducing-the-cloudfam-referral-program/">Referral Program</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/introducing-gift-cards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">18210</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Introducing the CloudFam Referral Program</title>
		<link>/introducing-the-cloudfam-referral-program/</link>
					<comments>/introducing-the-cloudfam-referral-program/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 02:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Discounts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=18081</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We are pleased to offer to our customers this full-featured referral program, the latest addition to our expanding rewards roster.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="blog-post-intro">Our commitment to continually improving customer experience and happiness is the foundation upon which we are built.</p>
<p>Sadly, we have found this to be an increasingly less common attribute among companies in the modern marketplace. What&#8217;s even more unsettling, this ever lowering bar is viewed as the norm by the frustrated and disenfranchised modern consumer.</p>
<p>It is with this inspiration in mind that we are pleased to introduce our new full-featured <em>CloudFam Referral Program</em>.</p>
<h2>Give 10, Get 10&#8217;s</h2>
<ul>
<li>For every person who you refer to us, we offer them $10 in store credit on your behalf.</li>
<li>For each and every person you refer to us who becomes a paying customer, we give you $10 in store credit.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Rules and restrictions</h2>
<p>There are only two requirements:</p>
<ol>
<li>First, you must <a href="/my-account/">have an account</a>, and be logged in.</li>
<li>Second, you must be a paying customer.</li>
</ol>
<h2>Get started</h2>
<p>To get started referring, visit the <a href="/refer-a-friend/">Refer a Friend page</a>.</p>
<p>You can keep track of all of your referrals by clicking on the <a href="/my-account/referrals/">Referrals tab</a> in the My Account section.</p>
<h2>CloudFam Rewards</h2>
<p>This <em>Referral Program</em> is only the latest addition to the ever-expanding discount roster we are proud to offer to our loyal customers.</p>
<ul>
<li>10% cash back on every dollar you spend is deposited into your account as CloudCoins, redeemable on future purchases.</li>
<li>15% discount on every purchase for all active/retired: military, police, fire-fighters, first-responders, and EMS. If you&#8217;re one of these heroes, contact <strong>heroes at cloudchemistry [dot] co</strong> to get your discount code. You will be asked to produce ID.</li>
<li>15% discount on every purchase for college students. If you&#8217;re a college student, contact <strong>students at cloudchemistry [dot] co</strong> to get your discount code. You will be asked to produce ID.</li>
<li>Free shipping on orders over $50.</li>
<li>50 CloudCoins ($5) deposited to your account as soon as you sign up. (For new accounts only)</li>
</ul>
<p>This is just the beginning. There is more coming soon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/introducing-the-cloudfam-referral-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">18081</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy e Liquid Online The Right Way</title>
		<link>/how-to-buy-e-liquid-online/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-buy-e-liquid-online/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 21:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buying Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[buying guide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[e juice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[e liquid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vape juice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dev-cloudchemistry.pantheonsite.io/?p=3983</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Why write this&#160;guide? Who is it for? If you&#8217;re reading this, you&#8217;re one of two types of people. You&#8217;ve never ordered e Liquid before. You&#8217;re tired of the nasty vape &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="ast-button" href="/how-to-buy-e-liquid-online/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">How to Buy e Liquid Online The Right Way</span> Read More »</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Why write this&nbsp;guide? Who is it for?</h2>
<p>If you&#8217;re reading this, you&#8217;re one of two types of people.</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>You&#8217;ve never ordered e Liquid before.</strong></li>
<li><strong>You&#8217;re tired of the nasty vape juice out there.</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>It really doesn&#8217;t matter. <em><strong>We&#8217;re glad you&#8217;re here!</strong></em></p>
<p>It&#8217;s&nbsp;nearly 2016,&nbsp;and the vape scene has been exploding with new vendors and juice manufacturers promoting their e-Liquid. With so many marketing tactics and products utilized by vape juice companies, it&#8217;s easy to get lost in a flood of emails or ads when trying to find your ideal mix, or just something new to put in the air.&nbsp;Although annoying, it&#8217;s actually nice to see the industry evolve into a formal marketplace that reaches millions of people worldwide. Whether you&#8217;re a smoker or someone who has never lit a cigarette, e Cigarettes offer a <strong>safer, healthier alternative</strong> to traditional (analog) cigarettes and offer so much more. With thousands of flavors to choose from, you&#8217;ll never be bored with your setup. Sounds great!</p>
<p>And here&#8217;s a big HOWEVER for you: Hopefully this isn&#8217;t news, but many&nbsp;companies honestly don&#8217;t care about the quality or efficacy of their e Liquid as long as it sells. This approach is often hidden under a slurry of marketing and promotion, but it&#8217;s very real, and it poses a&nbsp;serious&nbsp;problem for all vapers.</p>
<p><strong>We&#8217;ve written this guide to help vapers, new and veteran, get a better grip of choosing the perfect e juice.</strong></p>
<h2>Artificial Sweeteners in your e Liquid &amp; Vape Juice</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s no secret that&nbsp;brands like Equal<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> and Splenda<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> have been making an absolute killing by supplying the world with &#8220;safer&#8221; and &#8220;healthier&#8221; sugar substitutes such as Aspartame, Sucralose, or&nbsp;Acesulfame&nbsp;K. As with most things, something so shiny and sweet presents a dark side: many of these chemical additives are considered neurotoxins, and can (and have) caused adverse reactions in many people. Even though the vaping industry is young, it has&nbsp;undergone serious changes and growth through the years. One of these changes is the introduction of artificial sweeteners into e Liquid to make the vape juice blend &#8220;sweeter&#8221; or &#8220;smoother.&#8221;</p>
<p>Think about that for a minute. When you fire that device&nbsp;and inhale, <strong>what are you actually tasting?</strong> <strong>Is it authentic? <em>Real, even?</em></strong>&nbsp;The world works in funny ways, and even people with the best intentions take shortcuts. People with not-so-nice intentions make problems.</p>
<p>There are so many fly-by-night e liquid manufacturers to buy from,&nbsp;and Cloud Chemistry does its part to set a higher standard.&nbsp;In our observations,&nbsp;e liquids and vape juices with artificial sweeteners will decrease the lifespan of your coils. This is because the sweeteners create a caramelized build-up on the material that both wicks and vaporizes the e liquid. Over time, this build-up gets worse and you&#8217;ll notice less vapor production and, in many cases, a weird taste or odor coming from your coils. <em>Not yummy.</em></p>
<p>You know your body better than anyone else. But, when you&#8217;re choosing where to buy e liquid online, <strong>make sure the manufacturer avoids the use of artificial sweeteners at all costs</strong>.</p>
<h2>Is Diacetyl in your e Liquid?</h2>
<p>Obviously popcorn is delicious. Especially that smooth buttery kind that only a movie theater can produce. Mmmm. You know what&#8217;s not delicious though? <strong>Popcorn Lung.</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://www.cdc.gov/niosh/topics/flavorings/exposure.html#diacetyl" target="_blank">From the CDC</a>: &#8220;Diacetyl is a chemical that was found to be a prominent volatile constituent in butter flavoring and air at the microwave popcorn plant initially investigated by NIOSH. Diacetyl is also known as the alpha-diketone, 2,3-butanedione, or by its Chemical Abstracts Service (CAS) number, 431-03-08. Toxicology studies have shown that vapors from heated butter flavorings can cause damage to airways in animals (Hubbs et al, 2002). &#8221;</p>
<p>Not all e Liquid flavors use Diacetyl, but even with these health risks, some still do. When&nbsp;it comes to your health,&nbsp;buy e liquid online from&nbsp;manufacturers that <strong>do not use Diacetyl</strong>, or avoid it in almost all&nbsp;situations.</p>
<h2>How fresh is your e Liquid or Vape Juice?</h2>
<p>In today&#8217;s fast-paced &#8220;get it here now&#8221; world, warehousing goods is almost a necessity. In most industries, this is not a problem. However, in the vaping world, stocking e liquids is not ideal.</p>
<p>When purchasing e liquid online, <strong>choose a manufacturer that creates your e juice when you order it</strong>. This ensures a certain level of quality and personalization that large batches just cannot provide. For example, when you buy from <a href="/shop" target="_blank">Cloud Chemistry Vapor</a>, every bottle is made individually based on the options you select on each product page. When the order is received, our Flavor Specialists get to work on crafting your custom e liquid. It doesn&#8217;t sit on a shelf waiting for someone somewhere or a business to purchase it.</p>
<p>Freshness and purity&nbsp;should be a huge concern for you as a vaper. Quality loss is evident in many situations, especially when the business&#8217;s e Liquid is stored in less-than-ideal ways.</p>
<h2>How Involved is your e Liquid Manufacturer in the Community?</h2>
<p>E Liquid &amp; E Cigarette Manufacturing is an interesting industry. While they are legal everywhere in the US, e cigarettes have come under fire from Big Tobacco, the CDC, and even the FDA. These organizations&nbsp;are voraciously trying to to demonize the vaping movement as a whole, and&nbsp;paint it as just as bad or WORSE than traditional cigarettes. Most of this hate and mis/disinformation comes from the most obvious thing: money.</p>
<p>E Cigarettes and E Liquids are not taxed like cigarettes, and the government just doesn&#8217;t make enough money from&nbsp;sales of these devices and liquids in comparison to tobacco sales. Some states have even gone so far as to ban them in PRIVATE property. The grip is just going to get tighter as&nbsp;more people and businesses enter the vaping scene.</p>
<p>When searching for&nbsp;e liquid online, <strong>make sure you&#8217;re supporting an organization that FIGHTS for your right to choose a healthier (and tastier) alternative</strong>. <a href="/shop">Cloud Chemistry</a> is a vaper&#8217;s vape shop. We make sure to stay in-the-know when it comes to smear campaigns and remain above the curve when it comes to safe manufacturing practices and supplies. We care about the movement as a whole and we&#8217;re not in this for a quick-buck. Our goal at Cloud Chemistry has always been to help people stop smoking. Your right to choose is our lifeblood, and we&#8217;ll protect that&nbsp;as long as we can.</p>
<h2>How does your e Liquid Manufacturer Treat their Customers?</h2>
<p>After you’ve verified their standing in the community, you need to check to see how well the company treats their customers when you buy e juice online. Cloud Chemistry treats each customer as if they were our&nbsp;only customer, and help to get them set up with the best solution for their unique situation. Every person is different, with different tastes and preferences and should be treated individually. Any e liquid company that believes in one-size-fits-all approaches is a bad e liquid company.</p>
<p>Finally, you should verify that the company offers complete tracking information on your order, with a customer portal that will allow you to easily order e juice online again. If a company cares about you and helping you quit smoking, they will make it easy for you to complete your orders and re-order if necessary.</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s next?</h2>
<p>After you’ve thoroughly vetted and researched a <strong>quality e liquid manufacturer</strong>, place the order! Try your new, fresh e juice&nbsp;in your devices and crank it up! Get comfortable with your blends and invite your friends to try some of your e liquid. Any quality online e liquid company appreciates referrals, and will gladly reward you for sponsoring a smoker.</p>
<p>Welcome to the beautiful world of vaping, where you replace a harmful addiction with a pleasant one that benefits your health &amp;&nbsp;the health of those around you &#8211; <em>and your wallet</em>.&nbsp;Visit our <a href="/shop">online e liquid&nbsp;store</a>&nbsp;to learn more about our&nbsp;flavor-making process and to sample some of&nbsp;our delicious blends.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-buy-e-liquid-online/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>9</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3983</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
