<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Cloud Chemistry</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Premium eLiquid Custom Handmade to Order™</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 02:40:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.3</generator>
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">132433436</site>	<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Believe the Hype</title>
		<link>/dont-believe-the-hype/</link>
					<comments>/dont-believe-the-hype/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 02:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=23455</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LcCeaBYYeBM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/dont-believe-the-hype/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">23455</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stop the Flavor Ban</title>
		<link>/stop-the-flavor-ban/</link>
					<comments>/stop-the-flavor-ban/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=23187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As you most likely have heard by now on the main stream hype media, vaping is facing an existential threat, and we all need to pull together in solidarity in &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="ast-button" href="/stop-the-flavor-ban/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Stop the Flavor Ban</span> Read More »</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As you most likely have heard by now on the main stream hype media, vaping is facing an existential threat, and we all need to pull together in solidarity in order to safeguard our future, and to protect our right to use safer alternatives to smoking.</p>



<p>In addition to individual states like Michigan announcing flavored eLiquid bans, now President Trump has announced that he will seek a federal ban on flavored eLiquid products. This news comes in the aftermath of a recent bout of serious lung-related illnesses that the news outlets are saying were caused by &#8220;vaping&#8221;. But is this true?</p>



<p>While health officials continue to investigate the precise causes of these illnesses, we do know one thing to be true:</p>



<p>These illnesses were most likely caused by vaporizing and inhaling oil, not eLiquid. Specifically, cannabis THC/CBD vaporizers, blackmarket cartridges, and vape-able vitamins, such as Vitamin E, are all the primary suspects. However, this distinction is not being made in headlines, causing confusion in the eyes of the general public. When people see “vape,” they think eLiquid. As members of the vape community, we all know oil and juice are not even close to being the same thing.</p>



<p>Enhancing eLiquid with flavors not only provides a more pleasant vaping experience, it facilitates an easier transition into vaping and away from the harmfully addictive vice grip of tobacco products. Thousands of people depend on flavored eLiquid as a safer alternative to toxic, combustible cigarettes.</p>



<p>Please take a moment to sign the official <em>We The People Petition</em> to get our voices in front of policy makers who have the power to shield us from impending doom!</p>



<p><a href="https://petitions.whitehouse.gov/petition/stop-donald-trump-signing-federal-flavor-ban-e-cig-products">https://petitions.whitehouse.gov/petition/stop-donald-trump-signing-federal-flavor-ban-e-cig-products</a></p>



<p>Also, tweet your positive eLiquid story and tag President Trump:</p>



<p><a href="https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1172639954985455616">https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1172639954985455616</a></p>



<p>Be sure to share the above links with your friends!</p>



<p>At CloudChemistry, we have always valued the safety of our customers—and of ourselves! We all vape our eLiquid exclusively. That’s why we only source regulated, verified and tested materials for our flavor concentrate inventory. Quality and safety is of the utmost importance to us, and we strongly urge the vaping community at large to use only verified, tested materials in their eLiquid.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/stop-the-flavor-ban/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">23187</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>We&#8217;re Moving!</title>
		<link>/we-are-moving/</link>
					<comments>/we-are-moving/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=20011</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dear loyal patrons, With the changing of the seasons, change comes also to Cloud Chemistry. It is with great pride and excitement that we make the following announcements: Flagship Store &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="ast-button" href="/we-are-moving/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">We&#8217;re Moving!</span> Read More »</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Dear loyal patrons,</h2>
<p>With the changing of the seasons, change comes also to Cloud Chemistry.</p>
<p>It is with great pride and excitement that we make the following announcements:</p>
<h4>Flagship Store in East Stroudsburg is Moving</h4>
<p>On Tuesday, October 16, our flagship store located in Eagle Valley at 748 Milford Rd, East Stroudsburg, will relocate to the Price Chopper Shopping Plaza, 4543 Milford Rd, East Stroudsburg.</p>
<p>The Eagle Valley location will remain open for one additional week, and close on Monday, October 22, in order to allow our customers ample time to adapt to the change.</p>
<h4>New Location in Montage Mountain (Scranton)</h4>
<p>We continue to expand our dominant presence throughout Northeast, PA, with the opening of our third retail location in Montage Mountain, outside of Scranton.</p>
<p>Our regular <a href="/locations/">Locations</a> page will be kept updated with the latest information.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/we-are-moving/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">20011</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gift Cards Are Now Available for Purchase</title>
		<link>/introducing-gift-cards/</link>
					<comments>/introducing-gift-cards/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 16:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=18210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Happy is the heart that gives, especially when it gives custom eLiquid. 😀]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="blog-post-intro">In response to popular demand, we are happy to now offer gift cards.</p>
<p>The next time you&#8217;re in the giving mood, we&#8217;ve made the gift-card buying process extremely simple.</p>
<p>Some things to note:</p>
<ul>
<li>Gift cards are issued in the form of store credit <em>redemption codes</em> which are redeemable <strong>only</strong> in our online store.</li>
<li>Gift cards can be purchased in any denomination or quantity.</li>
</ul>
<p>That&#8217;s all there is to it. Now go spread the love.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;margin:2rem 0;"><a href="/gift-cards" class="button">Give some eLiquid!</a></div>
<p><strong>Quick Note:</strong></p>
<p>Don&#8217;t forget, if you&#8217;re the sort of happy customer to buy our stuff as a gift for a loved one, then you&#8217;re also likely to be the type who&#8217;d benefit from our <a href="/introducing-the-cloudfam-referral-program/">Referral Program</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/introducing-gift-cards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">18210</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
